To wrap up this video, here are a few comments on
为了结束这段视频，这里有一些关于以下内容的评论
implementing type checking in the presence of self-type. First of all, the extended
在存在自类型的情况下实现类型检查。首先，扩展的
subtyping and least upper bound operations can do a lot of the work. If you extend
子类型和最小上限操作可以完成大量工作。如果你延长
subtyping and least upper bound the way that we did then a lot of the rules don't
子类型和最小上界，就像我们做的那样，那么很多规则就不会
have to change and for the most part, you don't have to do anything special for self
必须改变，而且在很大程度上，你不需要为自己做任何特别的事情
type. Self-type can only be used in a very few places in the language and it's up to
键入。Self-Type只能在语言中的极少数地方使用，而且
you to check that it isn't used anywhere else. Those restrictions have to be
请您检查一下它是否没有在其他地方使用。这些限制必须是
followed carefully. And finally, for the most part, a use of self-type always
小心翼翼地跟在后面。最后，在很大程度上，自我类型的使用总是
refers to any sub-type of the current class. There is one exception to this in
指当前类的任意子类型。这方面有一个例外，在
the type checking of dispatch. In dispatch there's a method look up where we look up
派单的类型检查。在调度中有一个方法查找，我们在哪里查找
in some class C, a method F. And it's possible that, that method will have a
在某些类C中，是一个方法F。该方法可能会有一个
return type self-type. And this class here c, may have nothing to do with the current
返回类型自身类型。这里的这个类c，可能与当前的
class. We are dispatching here to a different class and whatever our current
班级。我们要派到一个不同的班级，不管我们目前的情况是什么
class is, this particular self type refers self type in That class, the class in
类是，这个特定的Self类型引用该类中的Self类型，而
which we're doing the look up, not whatever class in which we're doing type
我们做的是查找，而不是我们在哪门课上输入
checking. And fortunately we never need to compare that self-type to any self -type
正在检查。幸运的是，我们从来不需要将这种自我类型与任何自我类型进行比较
in the current class so there's no cross talk between different kinds of self-type.
所以不同类型的自我之间没有串音。
And again this is the only place in the type checking rules where you look at a
同样，这也是类型检查规则中唯一可以查看
self-type that is not one in the current class. To summarize our discussion of
不在当前类中的Self类型。总结一下我们对……的讨论
self-type, self-type is still a research idea. It adds more expressiveness to the
自我类型，自我类型仍然是一种研究思路。它增加了更多的表现力
type system, and I think that's, yeah, easy to see, but you won't find self type
类型系统，我认为，是的，很容易看出来，但是你不会发现自我类型
in mainstream languages. Self-type by itself I think is not so important, except
用主流语言。自我类型本身我认为并不那么重要，除了
for the project that you're going to implement. Rather, the reason for
你要实施的项目。更确切地说，是因为
including self-type is to illustrate that type checking can be quite subtle. It's
包括自类型是为了说明类型检查可能相当微妙。它是
not all INT plus INT equals INT. There are actually are fairly sophisticated things
并不是所有的int加int都等于int。实际上有相当复杂的东西
and fairly sophisticated reasoning that goes on inside type checking In practice,
以及在实践中在类型检查内部进行的相当复杂的推理，
of course, there needs to be a balance between the complexity of the type-system
当然，需要在类型系统的复杂性之间取得平衡
and its expressiveness. So more complex type-systems are harder to learn and
以及它的表现力。因此，更复杂的类型系统更难学习和
they're harder to use effectively, but they also allow you to write more programs.
它们更难有效使用，但也允许您编写更多程序。